const data = [
    {
        id : 1,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 2,
        question : "1 + 1",
        answer: ["5", "3", "2", "4"],
        true_answer : "2"
    },
    {
        id : 3,
        question : "The derivative of e^x",
        answer: ["e^x", "e^2x", "e^3x", "e^4x"],
        true_answer : "e^x"
    },
    {
        id : 4,
        question : "Who are you?",
        answer: ["Unknown", "Lola", "Rather not say", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Ronaldino"
    },
    {
        id : 5,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Lebron", "MJ", "Kobe"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 6,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Luffy", "Naruto", "Goku"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 7,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 8,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 9,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
    {
        id : 10,
        question : "Who is the GOAT?",
        answer: ["Me", "Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldino"],
        true_answer : "Me"
    },
]

export default data